Now let's go to Harshada and understand all the
important
stocks one by one. First of all, producer sahab said
that let's discuss ICICI Bank,
why is this ICICI Bank on the radar, brother, this ICICI Bank.
You might remember that when ICICI Lombard was
blocked, then they had
bought the largest stake. Some more
stake is seen coming here.
They bought around 25 lakh shares in ICICI Lombard for Rs
431 crore. That is why that stock is on the
radar today on both the counters because yesterday
again updates were seen coming in the evening
that ICICI Bank has recently been seen increasing its stake here.
ICICI Lombard, that is,
ICICI General Insurance GI, which is
continuously in this,
when Indian Enterprises had come out in the large trade and some
funds had sold,
most of it was absorbed by ICICI Bank.
Now the additional chunk has been taken up, so
ICICI Lombard is on the first dart and
along with it, I am coming to you sir.
Banks were on the radar, so ICI, you said that you are
not enjoying the private sector, hence I am going
with the government sector.  So,
along with Lord's, please check ICICI Bank as well. Tell me
what do you think this series will be at what threshold it bridges.
Then you will see the strength and
then you will become bullish on ICICI Bank in the series.
Ashish ji, in the private
banking space,
ICICI Bank is the strongest. Its previous
swing was around 1040, it has
taken support above that and is also holding 20 dema. So,
I feel there is
an opportunity here. I was avoiding it only
because there is a gap resistance around 1070 on the daily chart.
But I feel that if
someone wants to buy as per the risk reward, then
1035 is a
very strong stop loss for you.
For now, keep the target at 105 because there is a resistance.
But if we close above 1075, then
we can cross the zone of 1100 very comfortably.
Well, in one stock, before
moving further, I want to take in big stocks.  I wanted to buy it
but there was no reason so I did
not buy it. Yesterday we were talking about Berger Paints
at closing, please
show me its chart once because there was a great move in the spot market, there was a
move of around 10 points, it
obviously came down to 75 after adjustment,
but put the March futures in front of it, at
that time we had talked about March futures, there was a discount of around 64 points in March futures,
now it has become 53
points because obviously that
adjustment happens in cash, it does
not happen in futures, I was not able to understand
why it is so because we had
also brought that call of 550 and we discussed the call buy of 550
in 202, it had
reached 35 only then but even after that I still do
not understand the reason because
we have Shilpa ji and Prashant ji, I want to
ask them, have they done any study on this,
Shilpa ji, has done any study,
why is there such a big discount in Berger Paints
and is any thread being made  Is it true that
here,
as we discussed yesterday with Anuj
ji, usually in the market, the trend is towards corporate action,
but there is something here which is
not reflecting it, so the
setup here is definitely very bullish,
whether you talk about the chart or you
talk about the option change, you can see that the
levels of 630-650 are appearing to be very easily viable,
so here I think
today in the opening you should get this slightly adjusted price in
spot and futures, then you know we should take
a trade if it
sustains above 600, then it is a very
clear cut buy for targets of 650 to 660 in this
series, in futures or cash
or both will converge, no, if the
spot future sustains now 600 because the
option change always goes and sing with the spot
price, so here if the spot crosses and
sustains now 600, then it is a
very clear cut buy that here  There will be an upside
move and I believe that today
you should probably get it at the adjusted price in the opening,
exactly because if the
option changes according to the spot, then the
call of 550 should not be at a discount, the
entire month of March is still left,
but that was it, Prashant ji, did you
analyze it, Anuj ji, the difference is
clearly visible, but as
Shilpa ji said,
nothing like split bonus is visible in the corporate action, neither is
dividend visible, so I checked
that overall if we see, the volumes were
very strong yesterday, so my opinion is exactly
with Shilpa ji, if we
sustain in the spot above this zone of 600 610, then I
feel that both of them should come together
and the option price will also catch up and
definitely the effect of spot should be
visible in the option price, so today
in the first half, I will definitely
keep the stock on radar and its call of 500
50 and 600, keep both of them on radar.  Let's keep it
brother, this was a divergence in the prices of both,
that's why I mentioned it and there doesn't seem to be
any valid reason why there is such a steep
discount. Now let's move ahead. We talked about
ICICI Bank and ICICI
Lombard, but the last one has to be kept on the downward slope.
Manas, keep it for four days. I will come to you.
Harsh, what updates are coming?
What a wonderful thing L&T has done. In fact, L&T has
commissioned its own intelligently built hydrogen electrolyzer. This has happened
at the Hazira plant. Basically,
after this, the company will be seen doing forays.
Now its power capacity in the domestic electrolyzer plant is
around 1 megawatt,
which can also go up to 2 megawatts. Now, basically,
what is its purpose? It will enable the company to have
more integration, better
integration. The
company will be able to participate in more global competition bids for green hydrogen projects. Not only this,
many companies are investing in the many green hydrogen plants that are coming up in India. In
fact, for that also, the
company is seen participating as a public private partnership.  If it
gives
better equipment,
L&T will get a chance to participate in grid hydrogen projects.
Hydrogen
electrolyzer is actually made by itself. It has been
commissioned. Well, if not L&T, then who else can do it.
How about looking at the charts? The charts look good
because I think the stock had
formed a base around the 100 day moving average. Just a
few days after the correction, and keep in mind that
where the 100 day moving average is, there is
also a 20 week moving average near it, so the base
is formed. Now only waiting for a
breakout above 35 25. I
think L&T
will try to fill the gap that was there on January 31. In that case,
you can see prices up to 36 25 36 30.
In my opinion, you should buy. Stop
losses will be below 3405. This is a
good development. You will see the loan to buy increasing
towards manufacturing of domestic electrolyzers. This is
great news for you.
Bhaiti sahib, keep the Vedanta data ready,
keep the chart ready, I am coming, the global mood
is good but there is some
troublesome news for them, what are the updates, the
market was expecting for the broken Corin plant that
maybe now they will get the
go ahead from the Supreme Court that the plant can be
restarted, the Supreme
Court has again rejected that plea, the
Supreme Court
believes that repeated violations are taking place, that is why the
unit has been closed, so
due to environmental cause concerns, in fact you will remember that the
broken Corin plant is not functioning for a long time, they file
applications every six months that
we have fixed this thing, we have fixed that thing,
but still the Supreme Court is
not giving any decision in their favor, this is a set back, a
set back for Vedanta, tomorrow perhaps they will be doing
Hope Right, yesterday before leaving,
Vedanta was closed with great strength,
but now there is a setback from the Supreme Court, the unit will remain
closed, repeated breaches and serious
violations, this Supreme  I am telling you in court words
why should you get it rejected, brother,
what should I do, brother, how is the situation on the
charts? Yes, yes, yes, yes, on the charts,
pressure is visible. Yesterday, a slight
pull back was seen, but the speed at which
shorts were made in the last 15 days is
clearly viable and the stock was
not able to surpass 20 demas in any pull back.
Even yesterday's close
closed in the lower zone of its bullish band, so we feel that the
pressure will be seen increasing here today.
Based on the news, Quali
advises that the stop loss should be
maintained around 270. We feel that
levels up to 260 can be seen in this, there will be
pressure. Yesterday, it
definitely moved towards the end, but it is probably
preparing to go to 260. Now that the metal has been touched upon,
Hindalco was discussed upfront as a
big stock in the programming, let
us also understand its placing
on the charts at this time or how is the build-up
Shilpa ji, Hindalco, like Vedanta, was
showing good moves while going down. Hindalco had
also made a very good trajectory change from the lower level,
changed gears.
Going to the day's high, Andal has closed at 504.
How does it feel? It has just closed above 500.
So here I think the
levels of 525-540 will definitely come. So
here you have to maintain a small stop loss of 495.
This is correct. If it
sustains above 500, then it will be a very
good trigger for you for a quick move
towards
540. Yesterday, Nifty's top loser was Apollo
Hospitals. Weakness of more than 4 points reached the
day's close. Pressure
mounted throughout the day. Not only this, all the hospital peers were in the
same situation yesterday. GPT Health Care was about to be listed, in the
meantime, the stock was left in that too.
Some Nomura Singapore
sold a big change. Well, Apollo Hospitals is kept on the screen.
Right now,
Satpati Saheb, I will come to Satpati Saheb's charts.
I will
first see your story on this.  Jefferies is saying that the
report that is
going on regarding the litigation is at a
very early stage. It is unlikely that there will be
any near-term adverse impact from this. They are saying that there is a
weakness buying opportunity.
CLS is saying that we will
retain our outperformance call. The
target is 7000 for the share. This is negative.
Whatever is happening for private hospitals,
but it is very difficult to implement it.
Parthiv, what are your
fundamental views on this decline? Are you buying anywhere on Apollo
Hospitals or Hospital as a Space? If
I talk about Apollo Hospitals first, my
biggest concern here is the
valuation. And if any
regulatory hurdle comes, we have always
seen that over the course of time there is a
big correction in the stock. So, not at
these levels for Apollo Hospitals,
we will avoid the valuation here. I feel
that going forward, there will be good money to be made in this space,
but I think one will have to be
selective. We, Narayana  Rutalaya, an SAA
hospital stock, looks very good. The
management pedigree here is extremely
strong. Their strategy, the way they do
capex, I think it's a very good asset-
light type of business model. So, I
feel that scale-up can be good here. So,
overall, I think we will have to remain selective
in this hospital sector because it is a very
cap-intensive sector. But
fundamentally, if we want to
buy in some decline, if we want to buy something in the midst of this overhang that is forming, then
NH Narayana Hridaya, not Apollo, seems to be the best pick. At
this time, Parthiv, now that we are
talking about hospitals, let's discuss medicines.
Many pharma stocks are in the market today.
Which ones and why? We will start with Suvan Pharma.
Suvan Pharma has actually
announced that it will be merging with Hans Life Sciences, a
Hyderabad-based company. So,
shareholders of Hans will get 11 shares for each and
Suvan shares for each.  295 shares of
Co Hans. In this, you have to keep in mind
Adventus and Adventus is actually a 50%
stakeholder in Suvan Pharma. So,
Adventus has actually taken the initiative towards merging both the companies. In
that sense, Adventus will then
hold a 66% stake in this entity
and 33.3% will then be seen going into the hands of public shareholders in this merged entity.
This development
seems to be coming for Suvan Pharma at the moment and
keep Bindo Pharma on the radar. The USFDA
inspected their Ujia SE 2D facility
and this facility has come under much discussion. Seven
observations have been issued in their hands. There are
two developments for Biocon. One,
Biocon has signed a licensing pact.
Janssen Biotech and Johnson & Johnson
will commercialize B Mab T 1200
in the US. The primer is a biosimilar which is
used in the treatment of psoriasis and psoriatic arthritis. So,
that is a development as well.  The
Biocon biologics facility was inspected by the USFDA
and four observations were found. Now the company is
saying that it will submit a comprehensive corrective and
prevention plan for this facility to the
US FDA as soon as possible
and the company will be seen addressing any observations as soon as possible. So,
these three pharma
companies which are in the news today, please
keep all three on the pharma chart. Chatu saheb,
first of all, Apollo Hospital.
What is the mood after yesterday's week? I forgot to
come to you. Apollo Hospital. I remember the
day before yesterday I had given a sale on it. It was at
7000, sorry, or 7. We had
worked with a target of 7200 and
after that 7000. So look at the structure, Aash ji, Apollo
Hospital is weak but I think
this fresh sale will definitely not happen
because the pressure that was there in front of the expiry,
I think it will fizzle out somewhere. So
see here, the resistance that will be there will be around
6200.  I think that
in any pull back that comes, it will
face resistance somewhere here, so there will be
resistance of 6200, but
I think this fall will
come in continuation after a pull back, whose
target is around 5800-5850, so see, the
trend is weak, but if we want to sell, then
we have to adopt a sell on rise strategy,
where its positional stop loss will be at 6400, it was
not there and here comes the sell on rise
strategy on Apollo Hospitals,
Sawant sir, you got the data of both Biocon and Aurobindo
late, I am coming to
you on both, after the last US FDA
inspection, Form 483 is coming,
some objections are coming with Form 483,
what kind of objections are there, that is a different matter, how
deep are the stains, how light is that is a different matter,
but there are stains on both, which means basically bad news
and seven observations for Bindo for Biocon
Biologics, four objections for Biocon's mango,
four
observations, is there any opportunity for a trade bud, or is this
Similarly, the closing was becoming weak in the last few days,
if we compare both of them, then Biocon has been
quite range bound and is registering the zone of 295 300 every time,
so I feel that
here the better opportunity will be
in Pharma because the
higher time frame of Pharma is
quite bullish, so if there is any decline here and
we find this stock around the zone of 990 1000, then
we
can buy the position by placing a stop loss of 960, 960 and from
here you will have to keep your target
of 1100, so if there is weakness in the counter then
prefer Pharma, I want to avoid Biocon,
Bhati sahab, please open any OMC,
BPCL, HPCL, IOC, if you like any of them for
trading, then you should check it from today,
I am coming with an interesting report of HSBC on oil
marketing companies,
first keep the stock of BPCL,
Doctor sahab is saying this on the screen to
buy  Opportunities of 860 target of 860 is
running at 600 B Bring BPCL HPCL on the
screen HSBC has called target of 630
no no show the stock of HPCL
Doctor sahab the target is 630
HPCL is running at this currently at 500 and
IOC has a target of 185 and at this time the latest
equation should come on your screen
Meaningful upside HSBC is still
expecting it is saying that rates have been reduced
but there is still a lot of room for them to
move The range bound global crude
prices will support their profitability
in the near term The
benefits of refinery upgrades are yet to come
and perhaps valuation multiple revisions are happening
because government intervention
is continuously reducing and there is also tax support The
government's strength sir is there is
positional strength in any OMC Yes
Ashish ji see a little weakness is visible in all the three charts
profit taking
Higher levels are visible on the daily
charts, but if I talk about HPCL and
BPCL, they have a little more
strength because they are trading near the 20 dema.
We haven't seen such a massive decline, so
we think we might see a
pullback. After a bounce off the 20 dema,
a good movement could be seen after a breakout of 20. The
levels to keep in mind for buying HPCL and BPCL are: I
think 500 and 15 for HPCL. If it
moves above that, then a bullish
trade can be made. In that, we think we might
see levels back up to 550. So,
buying HPCL is recommended above 515. Similarly,
our advice for BPCL would be that
if it trades above the 615 zone,
a position can be created there as well. So,
buying BPCL can be done above 615 and HPCL above 515.  It is a
conditional buy which Thrush Hold Bati
sahab is mentioning, first of all,
try and place trades on it, after that take a bullish
call. Today is the expiry day of Sensex and
today is the beginning of a new month. It is 1st March,
so the auto sales numbers of last February are to
come.
Gaba sir, if
you like any auto OEM then keep it ready, I will
come to you on the charts and you have the same
Thar which is getting upgraded, it looks very good,
you check the charts, I am
coming for OMS, it is not left out, there is
no feeling of left out, Arjana, what are the
expectations, Ashok Leyland will remain on the red,
sales may come down to around 9 here,
anyway we have seen that the stock has been
in the grip of some profit booking in the recent past,
whereas some improvement will be seen in the auto sales figures.
On the two wheeler side, annual growth is estimated at 25% in Bajaj Auto.
In the case of ROI, annual growth is estimated at around 12%.
This month is also being predicted for TVS  It will turn out a little
better. Annual growth has been estimated at 28%.
Similarly, if you look
at the passenger vehicle side, then
this month too, i.e.
in the month of February, tractor sales may
decline to 13% for MNM. These are in fact
expectations.
Okay, these tractor sales may decline a little.
But I was reading the Chief Economic Advisor's statement yesterday.
I was reading the GDP numbers,
after which he said that perhaps this time the
situation will start improving from the farm and agri side.
Now let's see how it plays out.
Everything will depend on how the monsoon comes.
But Baba Sir, which auto
seems to be the best on the radar? Do you feel like going bullish
or should we leave it? No, no, no, I
like Sona Kams, which is an exchange. As
you said, Sona Kams is trading
at 689-660. Its setup is very
good. We have got a record around 660. We just have to
place a stop below that. Actually, even if we do
n't place it, it will work. Its target is
around 800. It seems we will have to give it some time.
For that, but the higher time frame
chart is good. UPM expansion contracts are
happening and an UPM has started. Sona
Kams Bhai Saheb, 800 positional time may be required
but keep it on the radar. All other
important stocks news. What are you saying?
Manganese will remain on the radar today. Ashish. Here, in
fact, they have increased the prices of a particular product. There is
no major change in all other prices. So, the
prices of ferro grade have been seen increasing by almost 5%.
Chalet Hotels has
announced that they are acquiring 100% stake in Aayushi Poonam
Estates for Rs 315 crore. So,
that stock will remain on the radar.
An update came this morning where the
board has approved that whatever
inter-company agreements are
more independent in Paytm2 Bank,
that entity will be seen taking such steps for it in future
also. So, this update has come.
Tips Industries has
actually signed an agreement with Oneer Music,
under which Oneer Music will get access to Tips.  The
full extensive catalogue of Dilip Buildcon has been placed globally, so that in
fact will be positive for them. Dilip
Buildcon has received an order of Rs 1955 crore
from NHAI. There is a building project
in Chhattisgarh. Adani Enterprises has
sold its entire 100% stake in Wizz Technologies to Adani Infra. Rs 150
crore will come to Adani Enterprises, but
this is an inter-company transfer.
We had seen CMS Info Systems, here they were
seen to be making big blocks. The
Vice Chairman and Executive Vice
Chairman and CEO of the company have increased their stake
from Rs 2.62 to above Rs 6. So
that stock is also on the radar today.
Okay, keep all the stocks on your radar.
Quickly transition should be done.
Preparation for profit should be completed for Friday. You knock and let's
start with the first deal.